One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
The Experiment Begins!
Shinokuni Unleashed!
Caesar's Laboratory - Main Entrance
Open up!
Hey, open the doors!
Give us Smokey and Tashigi-chan back!
What's that? An airship?
Now then children, time to get off.
This is your home.
Don't just wander off again.
Thank you, Master.
Mister Sheep, candy please...
Please give us the candy now, Master!
My head hurts! Master, please give us the candy...
You'll get the candy soon, of course.
Go straight back to the Biscuits Room.
There's lots of candy waiting for you there.
I have to go to the research room.
So relax and savor it.
The delicious, delicious candy.
Let's go to the room! Show us the way, Mister Sheep.
This way, children.
The Biscuits Room.
Candy... now...
You! Listen carefully.
Once they're in the room, lock them in tight
so that they can't escape again, got it?
Roger that.
This place is scary!
What is it, you smelly brat?
Uh, I mean, young lady?
How about you go with the other children
and eat your delicious candy back in your room?
What? What's wrong?
You don't want to go back to the laboratory, do you?!
Get out of my way!
Usopp!
Master... please give me candy...
That's right. Come on home, children.
Please, stop! You can't go to him!
You wanna go back to your homes, don't you?
Heave-ho!
No! I really want to leave!
What are you talking about, kid?
It's cold outside,
and didn't you see what floor you're on?
Now, go back to your room.
No! Save me, lady!
Mocha?
Let's go get the candy now!
Oh, right!
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you!
Mister! Lady! Save me!
Hey, you! Get away from the door!
Geez, what a troublesome brat!
Save me, lady!
Lady!
The Ruins of Laboratories One and Two
Sanji-kun's body took a lot of damage...
but it's so sturdy.
Usopp!
Hang in there, Usopp!
You came here to save me, Sanji?
I'm Nami!
Why are you acting so disappointed?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Vergo.
Don't worry. I had some coffee and cookies.
That's strange, where are the cookies?
I didn't give you any.
Oh right, I didn't have cookies.
When are you going to begin the experiment, Caesar?
Shortly... Monet, begin the transmission.
Yes, sir.
I really wish that you would keep
your subordinates under control, Vergo.
I broke into a cold sweat when Smoker came here.
You're right. He's a wild dog that can't be leashed.
But that's all behind us now, isn't it?
Serves you right, Law!
You were helpless against Vergo, weren't you?
The deal I had with you was useful.
In return for being allowed to stay here, you'll give my subordinates legs.
I'd be very thankful.
However...
You're stronger than me,
but I'm the boss on this island.
If you want to stay here,
we'd better weaken your position somewhat.
I will not cause you any harm.
What must I do to make you feel safe?
I have a proposition, Trafalgar Law.
I want you to take care of
my dear secretary Monet's heart.
Are you okay with that, Monet?
Yes, I don't see any problem.
And in exchange... I want your heart!
That's the deal.
As long as we've got each other by the neck, you won't be tempted to do anything funny.
And I can feel secure, too.
I've always believed that you can't trust anyone.
You reap what you sow, as they say.
You must have already found out...
that now, Vergo has your heart.
Hey!
I suppose that even you couldn't have expected...
that Monet's smart enough to change her appearance and follow you.
Hey, are you alright, Traf?
She overheard everything that you guys are planning.
I'm disappointed, Law.
I thought we'd finally become very good friends.
So you were saved by your exceptional secretary? I should've paid more attention to her.
I let myself become sloppy
because you're such a blundering idiot.
Watch your mouth, brat.
That's amazing. You're still alive
even though that guy's got your heart?
At the mercy of your own power, Law?
I'd like to know what you did with my heart.
Over here! Smo-
Master, we're ready to start the broadcast.
Oh, really?
You escape death, for now.
Okay, begin.
Something's being projected!
What's this? Where is that? Is that...
a candy? A huge candy!
Little Smileys were scattered from the Blazing Lands...
Various New World Locations - Underworld Brokers
and will soon gather in the middle of the Frozen Lands.
Once they all join together again
and become the complete Smiley,
the experiment will begin.
Four years ago, an explosion utterly devastated
this island. It was a poison gas bomb, called H2S.
That is what Smiley is.
But last time there was a problem.
People who inhaled the poison were weakened
but they were able to find safe places to take shelter.
So I plan to give the weapon
from four years ago, Smiley, a huge treat.
One that will supplement the poison gas
to become a flawless weapon of mass destruction.
Today marks the birth of a new weapon.
Its name will be...
Shinokuni!
Land of Death
Frozen Lands - Central Area
It's coming!
Can't we get away from it?
It has completely merged together on this side!
Just what is that thing?
No time to worry about it. Just focus on running.
Excuse me, everyone.
There appears to be a huge ball ahead!
What's that?
It's in the shape of a candy?
There are people next to it.
Vegapunk's Dragon (Miniature)
Master, I can confirm a giant, gelatinous creature.
We think that it's Smiley.
Well then, we'll proceed as planned
and project Master's broadcast onto the mist.
Good.
Once you finish the job,
you have to escape or you'll be in grave danger.
Get on the dragon sleigh and hurry-
What happened?
We...
We've got a problem with the sled. It appears to be melting!
We can't use it like this!
Why'd this happen now?!
Is this some kind of chemical reaction? It's completely useless now.
The dragon is running away!
One thing after another!
What?!
What a terrible thing to happen!
Not very convincing.
Guys, just run!
Your protective suits are useless now!
Throw them off and run to the laboratory!
U-Understood.
Take off our suits?
Master's orders are absolute! He must have some plan!
Do what he tells you!
H-Hurry up!
Turn on, damn you!
What? Now someone's image is being projected into the air!
Ignore it. Just ignore it. Anyway, just run!
Smiley! I missed you!
It's been three long years!
Oh, yes, Smiley!
This brings back so many memories!
I've prepared a very, very tasty treat for you!
Stay! Stay now, Smiley!
Just a little bit longer!
Your Master's orders are absolute!
That's how I trained you.
Stay! I told you to stay!
I have so much I want to talk to you about!
Do you remember?
It all started, yes, four years ago...
A-Alright!
Alright then! You can eat now! Good boy!
He isn't listening to you.
He ate it.
He ate it! He ate the treat!
You ate it, didn't you, Smiley?
Be reborn.
So it'll become something even more terrifying?
A perfect weapon of mass destruction.
That's one big frog!
It's starting. Something's starting to happen!
But what exactly will happen?
Hell if I know! But it ain't gonna be good!
Whatever, we just gotta run to the lab,
like Master said.
Dammit! Why did the sled have to break now?!
Master!
He's acting weird since he ate that candy.
Was the candy really so delicious?
We must make haste!
Even those who defend this island are running for their lives.
It does not bode well for things to come.
I agree.
Well done, Smiley.
Farewell.
Greetings to the newborn...
The weapon of mass destruction, Shinokuni!
Change the landscape of this island forever!
Hey! Wait for m-
My legs!
What's going on?
Save me...
What happened to him?!
Does it matter?! Just run!
My body...
won't... mo...
Run! Just run!
Master!
Yes! It was a success!
Not a single soul can escape!
This is perfect.
The problem with the previous experiment was that there were survivors.
The poison worked but they could still move a bit
so they managed to escape.
But!
It would've worked much better
if I had been able to freeze them!
This gas coats the body like ash.
It is absorbed through the skin and paralyzes the entire body.
Now, my perfect weapon of
mass destruction, Shinokuni!
Show me more! Show me the ultimate hellscape!
What is this?
The people are...
Save me!
...freezing solid!
Hey... what is this?
What is this terrifying video?
The ones who died looked like Caesar's subordinates.
What the hell is that purple smoke?
By the way, what country are they showing?
Well, you better not look behind you.
No way! It was happening on this island?!
Master!
Crap! If we don't run, we'll end up like them!
It doesn't matter!
There isn't anywhere on this island we can run to!
Oh, I see! That's why they sealed the laboratory!
To keep the gas out!
Open up! Caesar! Dammit!
I ain't gonna die out here like that!
Dammit! Dammit! Quit messing around!
Open up!
Run away!
Things don't look good!
You guys run as fast as you can!
If you get caught, I'm leaving you behind!
Zoro-san! At this rate, we're all going to...
Unidentified object spotted at 12 o'clock!
What is that?!
It's a...
dragon!
A dragon?!
Don't be stupid! Dragons aren't real!
They have them on this island!
But this one is a lot smaller than the first one.
Hey. Maybe we can capture it and fly away!
That's a splendid idea!
It's decided! We can't keep this up forever!
We're gonna capture him!
Hold it right there, Dragon!
It's my crew! They're being chased by the smoke!
Dragon!
What are they doing out there?
And what kind of running do they call that?
It seems the samurai's body is complete again.
Hey, you're right.
So I guess he won't be giving me his legs again.
Hey Robin! This isn't the time for that!
Hey, you guys! That smoke's bad stuff!
Run awa...
It's impossible. If I try to yell...
Damn Sea Stone.
Oh, are they your friends, Straw Hat Luffy?
As I'd expect from the great
Straw Hat Pirates, they're quite tough.
But they're just seconds away from
being killed by the gas.
And it'll continue to spread...
until nothing can live on this island. A land of death!
Nobody outside of this laboratory will be able to survive.
Of course...
that will include you, too!
What?!
Now, let's show the world...
that against my weapon of
mass destruction, Shinokuni...
a 400 million bounty,
a Navy Vice-Admiral,
and even one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
are all helpless to save themselves from dying!
What should I do? What should I do?
He's doing something with Luffy and the others!
What should I do?
I want to save them, but with this injured body I'd just get captured.
If that happens, then all my efforts to investigate the drug and get the sedatives, will be wasted.
What should I do? What should I do?
That was dangerous. I was almost spotted.
Hm? Paper?
"Don't do anything"?
Who threw this?
Could it be?
Smokey!
Tashigi-chan!
Thank goodness you're okay!
No... They're still captive!
Dammit! We're all gonna get killed after all!
Smokey! Tashigi-chan!
Our men?
But more importantly,
That really is a well-equipped laboratory.
You're right.
I bet a facility like that would have
the means to transport large machinery.
Why would you discuss
such things at a time like this?!
Hm, alright! At any rate, we're stuck.
I hadn't anticipated Vergo's arrival, but nonetheless...
Straw-hatter.
We don't have time to dawdle about in here.
The plan hasn't changed.
Make sure you don't mess up from here on out.
It's time for our counterattack.